msishopper.net 2011-12-28

# TrendSource and MSI Services Privacy Policy

** MSI SERVICES, INC.**

##  PRIVACY POLICY

Welcome to MSI Services, Inc. (the "Site").

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business.   
This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Field Agents") who visit without transacting business and Field Agents who register to conduct business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by MSI Services, Inc. (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Independent Contractors").

**"Personally Identifiable Information"**   
refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, date of birth, social security number, and photo identification. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?**   
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Field Agents. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Independent Contractors: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Independent Contractors, (Possibly add the application information that is obtained such as education, other companies they shop for, date of birth etc.) 

**What organizations are collecting the information?**   
In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party service vendors (such as clients we are providing services to that you as a Field Agent may be performing an assignment for) who may provide such services as  hospitality, retail, grocery, healthcare, insurance, property rentals(apartment associations), background checks, financial services etc. may collect this information directly from our Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors for identification purposes. We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them. 

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**  
We use Personally Identifiable Information to verify your identity, customize the Site and to make appropriate service offerings. We may email Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors about research or assignment opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information. 

**With whom may the information may be shared?**  
Personally Identifiable Information about Authorized Independent Contractors may be shared within the Site to compare with other Authorized Independent Contractors who we wish to evaluate potential improvements with our Field Agent Network of other Authorized Independent Contractors. We may share aggregated information about our Field Agents, including the demographics of our Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us on the Site. 

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by MSI Services, Inc. is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of MSI Services, Inc. except for use as indicated above. 

**What choices are available to Field Agents regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?**  
Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at 

[ Contact Us link under Support](mailto:TrendTeamSupport@trendsource.com).

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?**  
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Field Agents and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Independent Contractors. For example, if an Authorized Independent Contractor is logged on and the site is unused for more than 90 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Independent Contractor off.

**How does MSI Services, Inc. use login information?**   
MSI Services, Inc. uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

**What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Field Agents and/or Authorized Independent Contractors on the Site?**  
MSI Services, Inc. has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors.  
We do not share personally identifiable information such as social security or tax id numbers, photo id numbers or dates of birth. Contact information such as name, phone and/or email address may be shared with a client for assignment purposes in which case the Field Agent has given permission to do so.   
Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information.   
Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law: We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors. 

**How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?**  
All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as direct deposit information or social security numbers, is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Field Agents or Authorized Independent Contractors for any such occurrences. 

**How can Field Agents correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?**  
Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at 

[ Contact Us link under Support](mailto:TrendTeamSupport@trendsource.com) or by logging in to their Field Agent website at [ www.msishopper.net](http://www.msishopper.net/) to update their information under “My Profile”. 

**Can a Field Agent delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?**  
We provide Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's database by contacting 

[ Contact Us link under Support](mailto:TrendTeamSupport@trendsource.com) because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Field Agent's entry without retaining some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward. 

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?**  
We will let our Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Field Agent or Authorized Independent Contractor has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Field Agent or Authorized Independent Contractor to allow such Field Agent or Authorized Independent Contractor to prevent such disclosure. 

**PLEASE NOTE:**  
This Site is not directed at children. Field Agents and Authorized Independent Contractors are required to be eighteen years or older.  
**Links:**  
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours. 

© 2011 **MSI Services, Inc.** All rights reserved.  
Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials from this Site is expressly prohibited.
